dkmgames.com 2019-12-25

# DKM Games Privacy Policy

#### What is this Privacy Policy for?

This privacy policy is for this website (dkmgames.com) and served by DKM Software Pty Ltd and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it. The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations and requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy. 

#### What information do we collect?

The only information collected is when you register. We do not ask for personal information such as name and birthdate, only your email address. This address will never be given to third parties and is only used as an alternate to your user name when you login or if you forget your password.   
If you login via Facebook we do not access or store any personal information you have stored in that account.   
If you login via Google, we store your email and gender but never make use of your email or disclose to any third party. Gender may be used to gather user statistics. 

#### Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience by storing your game preferences and your login username so you do not need to login each time you visit the site. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors. 

#### Contact and Communication

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use. Effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.   
This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. 

#### External Links

This website generally avoids placing any external links. For any links that may appear from time to time, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned. 

#### Adverts

This website contains adverts as supplied by the Google Adsense program. Please refer to [ this Google page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) for any detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.   
As the ads are supplied by Google (who have tens of thousands of advertisers), we cannot have full control over which ads are displayed. However, we do attempt to block any categories of adverts that we believe may be offensive to our users.   
Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertisers website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned. 

#### Social Media Platforms

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively. Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms.   
This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
